CHRISTINA XAMIN

CONTACT

cxamin@gmail.com



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

Oakville, ON, Canada

SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML. CSS, and JavaScript
- Team player with excellent communication skills
- Excels using prototyping software including Adobe XD, Sketch and InVision
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- Easily adapts to new situations
- · Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way
- Comfortable engaging with stakeholders to gather data and requirements
- Able to map user journey through to completion

Ambitious designer with 6+ years experience in a professional design environment and a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design, video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Interaction Design Sheridan College

September 2014 - April 2018

Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College

January 2012 - May 2014

EXPERIENCE

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER Surrey Place, Toronto, ON

August 2018- Present

- Interviewed stakeholders (including partners and end users) to gather and determine requirements
- Developed wireframes and prototypes based on user research then organized usability testing for project development
- Successfully provided research and recommendations on multiple projects to meet web accessibility compliance

INTERACTIVE AND TECHNICAL MEDIA WRITER INTERN Rapid7, Toronto, ON

May 2017- September 2017

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT) Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- · Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy